I'm afraid the dinner will burn if I step away.
If it's someone trying to sell us newspapers again, just tell them we can't read.
You're not moving.
No one's home.
I guess that means it was a salesman.
Go away. We don't have room for all that.
Did your ears fall off? I said go away.
What's going on?
Get out of here. Ain't nobody got time for you.
It's my big brother!
Maria?
I'm so glad I found you!
I miss you so much.
Ew, gross. What are you doing in our house?
I told you we didn't want you here.
What's with the random visit? You okay?
I'm a fun time, play.
No, wait. Wrong phrase. I meant to say I'm a runaway.
Yeah, you may want to be careful with that.
Wait, you ran away?
Uh-huh.
You Ordinary story for the novelします.
Bye bye.
Bye okay.
Bye bye bye.
Bye bye.
That bossy old hag was always telling me how to do my job.
I told her my big brother would never talk to me like that,
so she said, that's fine, why don't you go and live with your big brother then?
So, you actually left and came over here?
Yep!
Hello?
Hey man, it's me, what do you do?
That's the worst impression of a guy I've ever heard, but nice try, Kate.
Good job, look how smart you are, I should have known you'd guess.
Right, well I'm glad you called.
Maria just showed up here randomly and I don't know what to...
I know, could you keep her for a couple days? I'd really appreciate it.
What? I can bring her back if you want.
Is she bothering you?
Well, no, but...
Uh, what?
School's out for a few days, so I guess it's cool if she stays that long.
You're the best, love you mean it!
No problem.
Oh, wow! I've never seen so much food in my life!
It looks just like Christmas!
Yeah? Well, not quite.
Is it someone's birthday? What's happening?
God sure has some annoying minions.
You're exactly what's wrong with the human race. Let's eat.
Ah! What the heck is wrong with you?
I don't remember seeing you pray for that!
I belong to the night tribe. I do not know this god of whom you speak.
Kobito, you don't have to give a sermon, but you can at least say thanks for the food.
Thanks for the food, I guess.
Nice. I'm proud of you.
Hey! You can't just start without us!
Oh, Heavenly Father, thank you for this food we are about to receive.
May it nourish our bodies and keep us strong!
Ah! Ah, sweet crap, baby!
Ah!
It's so yummy!
Um, I don't remember you finishing your prayer, hypocrite.
God will understand that I'm saving this chicken from the mouth of an evil vampire.
Whatever, that's cheating!
It's the truth!
No, it's not! You made that up!
Don't argue with food in your mouth, guys. You're gonna choke.
Yeah, hello?
Hey there, sexy. What color underwear are you wearing?
What do you want now, Kate?
Wow! You're good at this.
Anyway, no big deal. Just wanted to see if you're eating dinner.
Yep, they're at the table right now.
Okay, good.
Promise me you'll make sure Maria eats all her vegetables before dessert?
Uh-huh.
Great. Which one of you ate my dinner?
She did!
By the way, Maria, I'm really impressed that you actually found our house on your own.
I never would have been able to find it. The hag dropped me off here.
That's not exactly running away, then, is it?
Hello?
Hey, so how'd it go? Did Maria eat all her veggies?
She ate a lot more than that.
Good to know. Love you, mean it.
Love you, mean it.
Yeah.
Big brother.
Good, good, good news. I'll allow you to play a game with me.
Ah! Ah, look at that!
It's a porno game!
No, it is not!
Yeah, I don't believe you.
She's telling you the truth. It's a pretty normal game. Do you want to try it out?
Oh, heck yeah!
Ugh!
Ready? Fight!
K.O!
Aww!
You silly human.
How foolish you were to think you could ever be a match for me.
Not pulling any punches, are you?
And now, Darkness Requiem!
Come on! Please, you gotta wake up!
K-O! You win!
Coo-coo-coo. I win again. How predictable.
I was so close! Why did you throw magic on me at the last minute?
Let's go, guys. Time for you both to take a bath.
A bath? You mean all by myself at Big Brother's house?
Yay! I'm going first! Hold those, please! Thank you!
What the...
Hey, the bathroom is over this way.
Oh, whoops!
Me and Big Brother take the same bath!
Maria's taking a bath, Kate.
Make sure she scrubs behind her ears. She always forgets.
Are you actually that worried about her?
No, I'm never worried about anything ever!
Pretty. It looks just like fluffy white duty.
Hey, Maria. I'm leaving some PJs by the door.
They're cobatos, so they should fit. Don't stay in there too long.
I made white duty!
Ha! Watch this! Bam! Yeah!
Uh, Big Brother?
What's wrong, Maria?
It doesn't fit. Do you have anything else I can wear?
It's too tight, especially up here.
I don't think I'll be able to sleep in it.
Oh, okay. Sorry about that.
But I guess that means you'll have to find somewhere else to go!
Kobito, calm down. What's gotten into you?
Sha-ding!
Ah!
It's Big Brother's T-shirt!
Oh, my gosh! It's like we're connected!
You are quite a foolish, godly minion.
Once this battle is over, you will regret your mockery.
Please, your threats don't scare me, you smelly vampire!
Shut up!
I wouldn't do that if I were you!
K.O! You win!
That will teach you not to question my powers.
You're already exhausted?
Not worth it.
They say children grow best in their sleep.
I'm going to sleep, too!
What was that about?
All right. Time for me to pass out, too.
Oh, man.
Is Maria in bed? It's late.
She is.
Oh, good.
Hey, are you obsessed with your sister? Tell the truth.
I am not obsessed with anyone! Screw you!
What now?
Yeah, I need to know if she brushed her teeth before...
I will never sleep again as long as Maria's here. This has to end.
Just hang in there. We're almost done, okay?
Not so fast, kiddo!
Apologize to Big Brother for all the trouble you caused him.
Um, I'm very sorry for causing you trouble.
She's not the one who should be apologizing.
I owe you for this.
No, Big. I'm glad I could help.
So does that mean I can stay over again sometime?
Of course. You're always welcome here.
No, she's not! Don't ever come back!
I didn't ask you, you disgusting vampire!
I'll come back whenever I want! Big Brother said so!
Bye-bye!
Glad that's over. One more day and they would've killed each other.
Coo-coo-coo. Only stupid little babies run away from home.
Man, I guess that really got to her.
Die, fiend!
Hey, isn't it too early to be playing video games?
I must build up my magic skills to prepare for the random invasions of God's foolish minions.
Next time she's here, she will have no choice but to submit to my overwhelming powers.
Coo-coo-coo.
Next time she's here, huh?
Seriously, school's only been out for three days and already there's nothing left for us to do.
You make an interesting point. Do you have any idea what all the normal students are doing to kill time these days?
And how would I know that?
Rika has seen many manga where people are having hilarious parties together after finals.
Rika thinks they were called Forget Your Cares parties.
Oh yeah, I've heard of those.
I see. Yeah, okay, maybe we should give that a try.
What goes into planning something like that?
I didn't go through the stress of studying for exams, so I don't have any cares to forget.
Then I guess you're not participating with us?
I'm so exhausted from thinking about worrying about finals.
I understand. If you're that tired, maybe you need to go take a nap in the nurse's office.
But what do you mean? Come to think of it, Rika didn't take the exams either, so she's not stressed.
Um, teachers don't have to take the exams, but can I still come to the party?
Of course, if that's what you want to do.
Fine, I guess I'll go too.
Sorry, can't. There's only room for about six people at these kind of parties.
Shut up, you're just saying that to be mean. Why do you hate me?
All right, does everyone have a drink ready?
Rika does.
Okay, then drink up.
Wait, hold on a sec. Aren't you supposed to make a toast or something?
Oh, okay. This is a toast to finals being over. So, cheers and stuff.
Cheers and stuff!
Where are the snacks?
You gonna be okay?
I'm fine. This is embarrassing, but my body seems to have a bit of trouble with carbonated beverages.
Then why the heck would you pour yourself one?
I noticed it's what you're drinking, so I wanted to try it.
If I want to be as wonderful a man as you, I can't let a little carbonation get in my way.
Whoa!
Holy crap, are you sure you're good?
I'm fine, thanks. Forgive me for being such a useless servant to you.
Here, why don't I go ahead and drink the rest of this? Maybe grab some orange juice or milk instead.
Um, hey, big brother?
O-M-G! Interact Cat!
When did you turn nine? Please.
Hey, are you alright?
Orange juice? So is carbonation still hard for you to handle?
Huh? What are you talking about? Of course I can handle it!
I just don't want to, okay?
Still? Like, since when?
Um, nothing. Don't worry about it.
Crap, I forgot my past with Yozora is supposed to be a secret.
Something funny's going on here.
There. We already drank and ate snacks, so what's next on the agenda?
Do you guys want to play a game?
Party games are always fun. Rika thinks we should play the king game.
I've never heard of that. How do you play that one?
We all draw sticks to pick who's the king.
If it ends up being you, then you get to make another player do anything you want.
It's hilarious.
Anything? Really?
Like, if I wanted Yozora to lick the dirt off my feet, I could do that?
Yeah, the king's orders are supposed to be absolute,
so if you wanted to take it in that direction, you could.
Oh, yeah, I'm in. Let's play this Game of Thrones.
That's fine. Someone needs to put that dingbat in your place,
and I'm glad we'll be able to make a game out of it.
Uh, okay, hold on. We can only play this game under one condition.
We're all going to draw the orders out of this box,
so instead of one person doing it,
we all write down orders and place them in here.
Yeah, I don't think I like that rule.
Maybe if everyone faces the same risk, the orders won't be too brutal.
Okay, does everyone have a stick?
One, two, three! Show us the king's orders!
Heck yeah! I'm so the king.
I'll be. I'm the only one suited for that title anyway.
Stop trying to form words and draw an order, please.
You know, you might want to watch your mouth.
Talking to a king that way could get you in loads of trouble.
And the order is...
Number four puts on a swimsuit!
What? Four puts on a swimsuit? Who wrote that order?
That would be me!
Why'd you do that?
What if that command was drawn for you?
Would you want to put on a swimsuit?
The thing is, I would never draw my own order, silly,
so don't you worry.
Well, which one of you lucky ducks is it?
Who gets to hang around in a teeny tiny swimsuit
with practically your entire bod showing
while the rest of us sit back fully clothed judging you?
P.S. No one pieces are allowed.
It's me.
No! It can't be Kobito!
I declare this order invalid! It never happened!
My deepest sympathies.
But once a king's order is given, it is deemed absolute.
I know your innocence is threatened.
If you need someone to blame,
take it out on this tyrant over here.
It's not my fault!
But it's totally okay.
We don't have any swimsuits.
You can't swim in it, but I think mine'll work.
Oh my gosh.
I'm so sorry, Kobito.
I don't forgive you.
You are evil and you must be destroyed.
I'm sorry, I didn't think you would be the one to draw it.
Go!
Who's the king?
Oh.
Looks like it's me.
Ugh.
Seriously, you people disgust me to death.
Hey, who's number five?
Cause some jerk decided you get to read this out loud.
Yes!
That's me!
I win!
I'm number five!
Let's see here.
Oh, that's so good.
Yeah, I'm close.
I'm so close.
Oh yeah, right there.
Give it to me harder.
Yeah, harder.
Oh yeah.
You're sick.
Why would you want someone to read that out loud?
How did you know it was Rika?
She obviously didn't get what she was reading, so put that snarl away.
Rika hoped to see someone who understood turn red and squirm with embarrassment.
Gross.
Moving on.
Looks like I'm the king again.
And the next order will be...
Good afternoon.
Tell me, was someone with my face just in here?
Excuse me?
That wasn't me.
It was Lupin, you Rube.
Thank you and have a good day.
Which one of you monkey turds put that wad of crap on paper?
It doesn't even make sense.
Why would the king give herself an order?
That's the game, Miss Lobotomy.
All the king's orders are final and absolute.
Even the orders she makes for herself.
I guess we know who wrote that one down.
No way!
She dog-eared the corner so she'd know not to draw it.
Classic.
Forever the closet coward.
So, number one has to take off their shirt and show their chest.
Wow, that one's really low.
You go, Kodaka.
Way to stick it to him hardcore.
Slow down.
I didn't write that one.
No, he didn't.
That would be yours truly.
You've gotta be kidding.
And what if you had drawn that number?
Were you prepared to strip down?
And what makes you think that would ever happen to me?
I don't understand where this delusional confidence comes from.
All right, so who's showing us their jugs?
Because it's definitely not Rika.
Oh.
Mine are bigger than yours.
Okay.
This next round is the last one.
Which one of us is the king?
Oh, it looks like it's me again.
What?
Come on, little blue box.
Make Yozara lick my feet.
Hey, what is that?
It looks like there's one stuck to the bottom.
Okay, here we go.
This better be worthy of being the last order.
Are you ready?
It says...
Number three has to kiss the king on the lips.
Oh, Rika was wondering
if we were ever going to get down to the sticky stuff.
Fine, which one is number three?
I am.
Wow, you're going to kiss each other?
You're just like grown-ups.
Oh, awkward.
You guys all blow.
Let's get this over with Kodaka.
What? We're seriously going to do it?
We don't have a choice.
King's orders are absolute, remember?
I didn't make the rules.
Oh, yeah, the rules, right.
Oh.
Intermission!
Um, inter-what?
Not okay!
Why would you degrade yourselves in front of your peers?
Aren't you the one who said King's orders are absolute?
Shut up!
Both of you are above this stupid crap!
Are you possessed right now?
I've got it!
There, mission accomplished.
See?
This is Senna's glass.
So we just had an indirect kiss.
On the lips and everything.
I mean, that is still a thing, isn't it?
Are we in the clear?
Nope.
Just kidding.
Rika approves.
Yeah, I'll allow it, too.
It's okay with me.
Me, too.
So that means the King game is officially over.
Now let's go clean this mess up.
Uh.
Well, it wouldn't have been as good as just part of a game.
Hello?
Hey, sport.
Long time no chat.
Oh, hey, Dad.
This is a surprise.
Everything going all right?
How are you and Kogito doing?
Fine. We're both doing fine.
So what's up? Do you need something, or...?
Well, I'm hoping it's not a huge deal, but...
Zaki told me something the other day.
Who's Zaki? Oh, you mean Senna's dad?
That's right. Be honest, son.
Are you marrying his little girl?
What?!
That was kind of a messed-up forget-your-cares party, wasn't it?
It was supposed to be about relieving stress,
but it just made me even more stressed out.
The way you put that was incredibly poetic.
I learned so much from your words of wisdom.
You totally missed the point.
Oh, you need to stop being so modest.
This has nothing to do with modesty!
Join us again next time for A Man is Among Them.
That must be talking about me.
Oh, that's right. I always forget you're a dude.
Thank you.